//creating an array and passing the number, questions, options and answers

let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Who has the most NBA championship Rings?",
        answer: "Bill Russell",
        options: [
            "Kobe Bryant",
            "Michael Jordan",
            "Bill Russell",
            "Lebron James"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What does the NBA stand for?",
        answer: "National Basketball Association",
        options: [
            "National Bowling Association",
            "National Badmintion Associaition",
            "National Baby Association",
            "National Basketball Association"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which player has the most career blocks?",
        answer: "Hakeem Olajuwon",
        options: [
            "Hakeem Olajuwon",
            "Tim Duncan",
            "Dikembe Mutombo",
            "Kareem Adbul-Jabbar"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which player has made the most career 3pts?",
        answer: "Stephen Curry",
        options: [
            "Ray Allen",
            "Stephen Curry",
            "Damian Lillard",
            "Reggie Miller"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What is the most amount of points scored in a game?",
        answer: "100",
        options: [
            "81",
            "73",
            "69",
            "100"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "How many NBA teams are there?",
        answer: "30",
        options: [
            "28",
            "29",
            "30",
            "32"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Who is the shortest ever recorded player in the NBA?",
        answer: "Muggsy Bogues",
        options: [
            "Muggsy Bogues",
            "Nate Robinson",
            "Isaiah Thomas",
            "Kay Felder"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What is the maximum time a player can hold onto the ball, after passing the half court?",
        answer: "5 seconds",
        options: [
            "7 seconds",
            "10 seconds",
            "3 seconds",
            "5 seconds"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "How many fouls does it take for a player to foul out in the NBA?",
        answer: "6",
        options: [
            "5",
            "6",
            "7",
            "10"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Who is the greatest player of all time?",
        answer: "Lebron James",
        options: [
            "Kobe Bryant",
            "Lebron James",
            "Bill Russell",
            "Michael Jordan"
        ]
    },

]
